<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cultural participation of video game makers</title>
    <link>https://videogamemakers.page/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cultural participation of video game makers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020−2021. Raman Voranau, raman.voranau@mymail.unisa.edu.au</copyright><atom:link href="https://videogamemakers.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the project</title>
      <link>https://videogamemakers.page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://videogamemakers.page/about/</guid>
      <description>This website is dedicated to my research project undertaken at the University of South Australia. I interview video game developers, asking them about the following things:
 how your leisure looks like, what activities you prefer, why they are valuable for you.  Why is this important?   Participation in a range of leisure activities contributes in different ways. Customising our free time, we can achieve more meaningful leisure experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researcher</title>
      <link>https://videogamemakers.page/researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://videogamemakers.page/researcher/</guid>
      <description>Raman Voranau I have nearly a decade of experience in the cultural and creative industries. I worked in the museum of arts, event agency as well as in a not-for-profit organisation, where I administrated educational projects for the early career creative workers.
In 2017–2018, I completed the MSc programme at the University of Glasgow, doing research about digital creative workers and their international mobility. Currently, I am engaged in Masters by Research course at the University of South Australia studying leisure experiences of the video game makers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://videogamemakers.page/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://videogamemakers.page/team/</guid>
      <description>Researcher Raman Voranau, MSc. Masters by Research Candidate, University of South Australia, UniSA Business
Supervisor Professor Ruth Rentschler
Professor in Arts and Cultural Leadership, University of South Australia, UniSA Business
Co-supervisor Dr Boram Lee
Senior Lecturer in Arts and Cultural Management, University of South Australia, UniSA Business
Co-supervisor Dr Sandra Barker
Lecturer and Digital Learning Leader in Management, University of South Australia, UniSA Business</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
