<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leisure activities of video game developers</title>
    <link>https://videogamemakers.page/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Leisure activities of video game developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020−2025. Raman Voranau, raman.voranau@mymail.unisa.edu.au</copyright><atom:link href="https://videogamemakers.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the project</title>
      <link>https://videogamemakers.page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://videogamemakers.page/about/</guid>
      <description>This website is dedicated to my research project undertaken at the University of South Australia. I am interviewing videogame developers to ask you about the following things:
 What does your leisure look like? What leisure activities do you prefer? What are the leisure activities valuable to you?  Why is this important?   The global health pandemic has affected work and leisure activities. It is further blurring the border between work and leisure, causing us to question the value of meaningful leisure experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researcher</title>
      <link>https://videogamemakers.page/researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://videogamemakers.page/researcher/</guid>
      <description>Raman Voranau has nearly a decade of experience in the cultural and creative industries. His professional background includes working at an art museum, an event agency, and a not-for-profit organisation, where he managed educational projects for early-career creative workers.
In 2017–2018, Raman completed an MSc course at the University of Glasgow, conducting research on the international mobility of creative workers from Eastern Europe. Currently, he is pursuing a PhD at the University of South Australia, studying the effects of public funding on video game production.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
